A Guide to the Governor Robert F. McDonnell, Executive Office-Counselor's Office, Records, 2002-2003; 2006-2013 (bulk 2010-2013)
Library of Virginia
- II. Clemency Files, 2002-2003; 2006-2012 (bulk 2010-2012)., Extent: 3.5 cubic feet (10 boxes). (Box 6-15)
  - Mario Bustillo, 2002-2003 (2 of 11) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Mario Bustillo, 2002-2003 (3 of 11) (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Mario Bustillo, VHS tape, Univision WMDO, Washington, DC, undated (4 of 11) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Mario Bustillo, 2006 (5 of 11) (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Mario Bustillo, 2006 (6 of 11) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Mario Bustillo, 2006 (7 of 11) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Mario Bustillo, 2006-2008 (8 of 11) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Mario Bustillo, 2008 (9 of 11) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Mario Bustillo, 2008 (10 of 11) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Mario Bustillo, 2009-2011 (11 of 11) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Thomas Haynesworth, 2009-2011 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Thomas Haynesworth, Brief in Support of Unopposed Petitions for Writs of Actual Innocence, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Thomas Haynesworth, Exhibits to Brief, 2011 (1 of 3) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Thomas Haynesworth, Exhibits to Brief, 2011 (2 of 3) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Thomas Haynesworth, Exhibits to Brief, 2011 (3 of 3) (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Jerry Jackson Clemency Petition, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Jerry Jackson, Clemency Materials, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Jerry Jackson, Clemency Materials, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Jerry Jackson, Correspondence and Memoranda, July 2011 (1 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Jerry Jackson, Correspondence and Memoranda, July 2011 (2 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Jerry Jackson, Correspondence and Memoranda, July-August 2011 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Jerry Jackson Clemency - Exhibits, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Jerry Jackson Clemency - Court Opinions, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Jerry Jackson v. Loretta Kelly, 4/30/08-05/01-08 Hearing Transcript (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Teresa Lewis, Clemency Petition, 25 August 2010 (1 of 3) (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Teresa Lewis, Clemency Petition, 25 August 2010 (2 of 3) (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Teresa Lewis, Clemency Petition, 25 August 2010 (3 of 3) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Teresa Lewis Execution Notebook 1, September 2010 (1 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Teresa Lewis Execution Notebook 1, September 2010 (2 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Teresa Lewis Execution Notebook 2 (Exhibits), September 2010 (1 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Teresa Lewis Execution Notebook 2 (Exhibits), September 2010 (2 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Teresa Lewis Execution Notebook 1 (Staff Copy), September 2010 (1 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Teresa Lewis Execution Notebook 1 (Staff Copy), September 2010 (2 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Teresa Lewis, Clemency Petition Research, 2010, (1 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Teresa Lewis, Clemency Petition Research, 2010, (2 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Teresa Lewis v. Commonwealth, Supreme Court of Virginia, volume 1 of 2, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Teresa Lewis v. Commonwealth, Supreme Court of Virginia, volume 2 of 2, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Teresa Lewis Execution, News Articles and Notes, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Teresa Lewis Execution, Correspondence, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Johnathan C. Montgomery, 2012 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Paul Powell Clemency Petition Binder (Jasen Eige's copy), 2010 (1 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Paul Powell Clemency Petition Binder (Jasen Eige's copy), 2010 (2 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Paul Powell Clemency Petition Binder (copy), 2010 (1 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Paul Powell Clemency Petition Binder (copy), 2010 (2 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Paul Powell Execution, Correspondence, News Articles and Notes, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Davey Reedy Clemency Petition, Correspondence, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Jens Soering Clemency Petition, 19 January 2011 (volume) (Box 13)
  - Jens Soering Clemency Request Binder, 20 May 2011 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Jens Soering Clemency Request Binder, 20 May 2011 (copy) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Jens Soering Clemency Petition, Correspondence, 2010-2012 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Jens Soering Parole Hearing, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Darick Walker Execution Binder, May 2010 (Gov. McDonnell's copy) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Darick Walker Execution Binder, May 2010 (Jasen Eige's copy) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Darick Walker, Correspondence, May 2010 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Walker v. Kelly, Petition for a Writ of Certiorari, US Supreme Court (volume) (Box 14)
  - Walker v. Kelly, Petition for a Writ of Certiorari, US Supreme Court (volume) (Box 14)
  - Medical Pardons
    - Bryan M. Jenkins, 2010 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Teddy Justus, 2010 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Omare R. King, 2010 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Anna M. Sexton, 2010 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Medical Pardon Criteria and Examples, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - International Prisoner Transfer
    - Jung Kwang Kim, 2011 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 2011-20212 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - International Prisoner Transfer Program, 2010 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- III. Judges, 2011-2012., Extent: 1 folder. (Box 15)
  The Judges series is housed in one folder.This series contains confidential and privacy-protected records and is closed for 75 years per Code of Virginia, 2.2-3705.1, 2.2-3800 and 42.1-78.
  - Judicial Inquiry and Review Commission, Colon Whitehurst, 2011 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Judicial Application of Henry Otis Brown, 2012 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- IV. Attorney General Settlements, 2010-2011., Extent: 1 folder. (Box 15)
  The Attorney General Settlement series is housed in one folder. This series contains copies of settlement agreements between individuals and state agencies requiring the approval of the Governor. The agreements usually include a request for settlement from the Attorney General (Ken Cuccinelli) which provides the background of the case, an approval of settlement letter from the Governor to the Attorney General, the settlement and other supporting documents. This series contains confidential, privacy-protected and attorney-client privileged records and is closed for 75 years per Code of Virginia, 2.2-3705.1, 2.2-3800 and 42.1-78.
  - Settlements, 2010-2011 (Box 15, Folder 10)